{"data":{"allContentfulList":{"nodes":[{"name":"faqs","type":"faq","items":[{"question":"What is Routed? What problem does it aim to solve?","answer":{"raw":"{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"marks\":[],\"value\":\"Emergency room care is not one size fits all. And for that reason, an EMT with an inbound patient has many decisions to make and quickly. How soon can the patient be assisted? Who has beds available? Where can the patient's needs be met best? Routed brings the communication pipeline between the EMTs and emergency staff into the 21st century, providing in-bound transports with access to optimal care options and hospitals with better patient data to prepare them ahead of arrival. \\n\\n\",\"nodeType\":\"text\"}],\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\"}],\"nodeType\":\"document\"}"}},{"question":"Who is behind Routed?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"Code for San Francisco is a part of the Code for America Brigade Network, a volunteer civic tech organization that leverages 21st-century technology to solve problems and to make life easier for civil servants working in local government. The Routed team is a dedicated group of volunteers composed of project managers, software engineers, data analysts, full-stack developers, and designers, with experience in transportation, patient health care records, hospitality, government services, and logistics.\\r\\n\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"Who is Routed available to today?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"Routed has been coded in open-source. Although current deployment is targeted to the City of San Francisco, its framework can be replicated for other cities.\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"Is Routed intended to be used for all patients?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"At this stage, Routed is only intended for Code 2, or non-emergency, patients.\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"Does a digital ringdown replace the need for radio?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"At this stage, the digital ringdown within Routed fully replaces the need for radio communication with non-critical Code 2 patients only. \",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"Does the Routed platform incorporate all hospitals? All ambulance networks?","answer":{"raw":"{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"marks\":[],\"value\":\"The vision is for Routed to be used for all emergency departments in San Francisco and with all ambulance providers including AMR, King American, and the San Francisco Fire Department. For the beta test, only SFFD ambulances and the SF General Emergency Department will be participating. \",\"nodeType\":\"text\"}],\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\"}],\"nodeType\":\"document\"}"}},{"question":"How is patient information protected?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"No personally identifiable or non-HIPAA compliant data is collected within Routed.\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"Who has access to data from the Routed platform?","answer":{"raw":"{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"marks\":[],\"value\":\"EMTs, Emergency Department charge nurses, ED Administrators on Duty, hospital administration, and EMS division staff have access to Routed.\",\"nodeType\":\"text\"}],\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\"}],\"nodeType\":\"document\"}"}},{"question":"How often is the information on Routed updated?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"Digital ringdowns are updated nearly instantaneously once they are sent from EMTs. At this stage, hospital bed availability is updated ideally at a 1-2 hour cadence but is dependent on staff resources at emergency departments.\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"How does Routed interface with existing dispatch?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"For the purposes of the beta test, Routed will be used in parallel with existing dispatch operations.\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"What is the goal of the beta program?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"The beta test serves as an opportunity to test the product in a production scenario with a narrow and dedicated pool of end users. It is integral for collecting feedback and user research to identify issues and potential feature modifications prior to a full citywide implementation.\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}},{"question":"Why is Routed built on open-source software?","answer":{"raw":"{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"data\":{},\"marks\":[],\"value\":\"Routed has been developed as open-source to support easy access for other cities that are interested in reducing emergency department wait times and to help level-load emergency demand.\",\"nodeType\":\"text\"}],\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\"}],\"nodeType\":\"document\"}"}},{"question":"What if I don’t find what I’m look for?","answer":{"raw":"{\"nodeType\":\"document\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"Please reach out to our Team Co-Lead Joe Kaylor for more information or other inquiries. \",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]},{\"nodeType\":\"paragraph\",\"data\":{},\"content\":[{\"nodeType\":\"text\",\"value\":\"joe.c.kaylor@gmail.com\",\"marks\":[],\"data\":{}}]}]}"}}]}]}}}